Finding aid for the Bonnie Cashin Collection of Fashion, Theater, and Film Costume Design LSC.0440
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legal Documents and Related Papers, 1942 - 1999; 24 oversize boxes (233 folders)
  - Contracts and Negotiations, February 4, 1952 - August 23, 1982; 5 oversize boxes and 1 folder
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1960; 11 pages (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Cashin to Marcel Boussac (Maison Dior), and to Frank A. Johnson and Wayne A. Cawley (Endicott Johnson Corporation) regarding possible design partnerships., January 16, 1961; 4 pages (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Gail Leather / Coach Leatherwear., November 30, 1961 - February 16, 1973; 25 pages (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's. Cashin-Carry patent., 1961 - 1963; 28 pages (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Russell Taylor., November 14, 1961; 3 pages (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1962; 34 pages (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Modelia Inc., August 8, 1962 - March 1963; 3 pages (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Infanta Knitting Mills (children's clothing)., August 11, 1962 - April 22, 1963; 5 pages (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1963; 2 pages (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Ballantyne Sportswear Co., January 4, 1963 - December 7, 1964; 14 pages (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Co. (shoes)., March 20 - May 7, 1963; 3 pages (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Golo Shoe Company., April 15, 1963; 2 pages (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Hoffritz (Uniform design)., April 19, 1963; 1 page (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Ramy Alexander (knitwear, Peru)., February 15, 1963 - March 3, 1964; 7 pages (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sill and Co., 1964; 43 pages (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for I. Miller (boots)., February 19, 1964; 2 pages (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1965; 16 pages (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Samsonite., September 9, 1965; 1 page (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1966; 11 pages (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Lockheed-California Company., January 21, 1966 - January 20, 1967; 50 pages (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Turtle Bay, a division of Jonathan Logan., April 17 - June 26, 1966; 8 pages (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Hartmann Luggage., October 11, 1966; 1 page (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Sills and Co., 1967; 22 pages (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Vasa (furniture)., January 19, 1967; 3 pages (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co.; includes promotional material for Gene Burton (California boutique)., 1968; 79 pages; 3 booklets (Box 201, Folder 29)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Eugenio Ramalho Lda. (Portugal, knitwear)., January 4, 1968 - October 6, 1969; 29 pages (Box 201, Folder 30)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Hermes., March 26, 1968 - February 27, 1969; 4 pages (Box 201, Folder 31)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Aquascutum., November 4, 1968; 2 pages (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Harmon Knitwear., November 12, 1968- February 13, 1970; 5 pages (Box 201, Folder 33)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1969; 24 pages (Box 201, Folder 34)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Brueton Industries (furniture)., June 10 - December 15, 1969; 56 pages (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Scheinbart (eyeglasses)., October 29, 1969; 1 page (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Design Thai (textiles)., December 1969 - March 5, 1971; 10 pages (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1970; 36 pages (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Burlington exports (India)., 1970 - 1971; 81 pages (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Bonnie Doon Sports Hosiery., December 9, 1971; 1 page (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed licensing with perfume and cosmetics companies, with Jane Trahey as agent., March 17, 1970 - April 1973; 6 pages (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Levi's for Gals., 1970 - 1971; 22 pages (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Dawson International Limited., December 11, 1971 - October 25, 1979; 150 pages (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Crescendoe-Superb., December 23, 1969 - April 3, 1974; 129 pages (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1971; 31 pages (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for "Patternings," "Knit Flakes," and advertisement for Sears-Kenmore sewing machine commercial., 1971 - 1976; 55 pages (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Jonas Senter - Mitsubishi (shoes)., March 25, 1971 - April 8, 1971; 4 pages (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for C & L Ideas, "Leather, Suede and Fur Do It Yourself Kits.", May 17 - May 24, 1971; 7 pages (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for proposed Bernard Goodman / Sport Whirl, October 21, 1971 - February 29, 1972; 38 pages (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1972; 5 pages (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs with Otterburn Mill Ltd., December 23, 1966 - July 9, 1975; 63 pages (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1973; 17 pages (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Les Bernard (jewelry)., July 23, 1973; 2 pages (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Cashin designs for Eastern Airlines uniforms., September 1973; 8 pages (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Carroll and Co. (men's clothing)., December 17, 1973; 2 pages (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1974; 28 pages (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Originala., February 6, 1974; 6 pages (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for HBA furs., April 10, 1974 - September 29, 1975; 9 pages (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Evelyn Pearson., December 20, 1974 - December 8, 1975; 25 pages (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1975; 28 pages (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's Cashin-Carry trademark., February - March 1975; 5 pages (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Meyers., April 1975 - June 16, 1980; 117 pages (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Cashin Men to be manufactured by Bert Paley., July 9, 1975 - July 18, 1978; 106 pages (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Main Street Rainwear., October - November 1975; 5 pages (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Uniroyal (shoes)., January 18, 1968 - December 12, 1975; 13 pages (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Sills and Co., 1976; 29 pages (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Revillon., January 20, 1976; 5 pages (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for Pearl Bedell., April 2, 1976; 8 pages (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's proposed designs for China Trade Corporation, represented by promoter Don King., May 15, 1976 - September 16, 1976; 21 pages (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's International Management Group (IMG) representation., June 25, 1976 - August 23, 1982; 40 pages (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for D. Klein, February 10 - November 21, 1977; 15 pages (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Rein, Rame and Gurvitch (R.R.G.), March 20, 1977 - April 18, 1977; 13 pages (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding the dissolution of Sills and Co., June 2 - December 2, 1977; 53 pages (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Russell Taylor., August 23, 1977 - January 1, 1982; 27 pages (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Carter Leather Goods Co., June 1978 - February 2, 1981; 19 pages (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Aris - Isotoner Gloves, March 1977 - May 30, 1978; 24 pages (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trademarks for "The Knittery and "Bonnie Jean.", August 23, 1977 - January 12, 1978; 23 pages (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's designs for Ledaspain U.S.A. Inc., July 21 - August 23, 1978; 29 pages (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Documents regarding Qiana promotional videotape., January 29 - March 18, 1981; 12 pages (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Documents regarding liquidation of Bonnie Cashin Designs Inc., 1986 - 1990; 50 pages (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Clippings and Cashin illustrations regarding furniture designs for Brueton Industries., 1969-1970; 8 pages (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Caltech: James Michelin Lecture Series and Related Cashin Gifts, 1978 - 2000; 3 oversize boxes and 5 folders
    This subseries contains documentation of programs created and endowed by Bonnie Cashin at the California Institute of Technology (Caltech). The subseries is particularly rich in correspondence between Cashin and Caltech regarding the James Michelin Lecture Series, which she developed and funded.
    - Correspondence and research., 1978; 19 pages; 1 booklet (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and research., 1979; 23 pages (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and research., 1980; 35 pages (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and research., 1981; 28 pages (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and research., 1982; 27 pages; 1 brochure; 1 booklet (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and research., 1983; 6 pages (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and research., 1984; 23 pages (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and research., 1985 - 1988; 22 pages; 3 pamphlets; 1 booklet (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and research., 1989; 6 pages (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and research., 1990; 20 pages (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and research., 1991; 154 pages; 1 pamphlet; 1 booklet (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and research, including Gustavson Associates appraisal of Cashin oil royalty interests., 1991; 8 pages; 1 brochure; 1 booklet (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - "Caltech at 100" catalogue., 1991; 1 catalogue (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and research., 1992; 37 pages; 1 booklet (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer Vincent Scully., 1992; 19 pages; 1 pamphlet; 1 booklet (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer David Hockney., 1993; 26 pages; 3 pamphlets; 2 booklets (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer Tom Stoppard., 1994; 22 pages; 2 pamphlets; 1 booklet (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer Frank O. Gehry., 1995; 28 pages; 2 pamphlets; 1 booklet (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and research regarding Bonnie Cashin Prize for Imaginative Thinking and James Michelin lecturer Oliver Stone., 1996; 28 pages; 2 pamphlets; 1 application (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer Beverly Sills., 1997; 21 pages; 1 magazine; 1 booklet (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and research., 1998; 23 pages; 2 booklets; 1 pamphlet (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and research regarding James Michelin lecturer Seamus Heaney., 1999; 14 pages; 1 pamphlet; 1 booklet (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and research regarding proposed Cashin art pavilion., 1999; 41 pages; 1 magazine (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and research., 2001; 2 pages; 1 pamphlet (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Cassette recording: James Michelin Distinguished Lecture Series "Tom Stoppard: Playing with Science.", October 20, 1994; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 32)
    - VHS recording: James Michelin Distinguished Lecture Series "Frank Gehry: Current Work.", November 8, 1995; 1 video tape (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - VHS recording: James Michelin Distinguished Lecture Series "Oliver Stone: Film, Chaos and Mass Delusion.", January 28, 1997; 1 video tape (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - VHS recording: James Michelin Distinguished Lecture Series "A Conversation with Beverly Sills.", November 4, 1997; 1 video tape (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - VHS recording: James Michelin Distinguished Lecture Series "Seamus Heaney - Opened Ground - A Reading with Commentary.", February 25, 1999; 1 video tape (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Donations and Related Tax Documents, 1961 - 1993; 3 oversize boxes
    This subseries contains documentation of Bonnie Cashin's charitable donations and related tax papers. The subseries contains information regarding Cashin's donations of her clothing designs to various non-profit institutions.
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1961 - 1978; 21 pages (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1980; 2 pages (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1980; 16 pages (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Personal gifts from Cashin., 1980; 2 pages (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1981; 36 pages; 3 booklets (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's charitable donation to Cooper-Hewitt Museum., 1981; 2 pages (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's charitable donation to the Metropolitan Museum of Art., 1981; 8 pages (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1981; 26 pages (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Cashin's charitable donation to Museum of Modern Art., 1981 - 1982; 16 pages (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1981 - 1984; 12 pages (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Personal gifts from Cashin., 1981 - 1982; 9 pages (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1982; 26 pages; 1 booklet (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1983; 25 pages; 1 booklet (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1984; 44 pages (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1985; 22 pages (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1986; 67 pages (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Appraisals of Cashin's clothing and accessory designs., 1986; 18 pages (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Appraisals of Cashin's clothing and accessory designs., 1987; 9 pages (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1987; 39 pages (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Appraisals of Cashin's clothing and accessory designs., 1990; 16 pages (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Cashin's charitable donations to various museums, schools and causes; including cash gifts, artwork, and Cashin designs., 1990; 108 pages; 22 checks in envelope (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Federal Trade Commission investigation into Bonnie Cashin Designs Inc., January 8, 1976 - May 6, 1976; 52 pages (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Accounting paperwork., 1990 - 1992; 102 pages (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Appraisals and tax documents., 1993; 90 pages (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Letters of support regarding IRS inquiry into value of Cashin's clothing and accessory designs., January 1994; 15 pages (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Innovative Design Fund (Legal Documents), 1979 - 1988; 9 oversize boxes and 2 folders
    - Notes, quotes, and essays regarding formation of I.D. Fund., ca. 1979 - 1981; 94 pages (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Outlines, procedures, form letters and correspondence., August 1981 - July 17, 1987; 73 pages; 2 booklets (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Appeal letters and thank yous., ca. 1982 - 1985; 21 pages (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Award committee memos., ca. 1983 - 1987; 4 pages (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - I.D. Fund brochure., May 16, 1984; 1 page; 1 brochure (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Press kit., November 1986; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings regarding I.D. Fund., 1978 - 1988; 91 pages; 8 pamphlets (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings regarding I.D. Fund board members and I.D. "type" people., 1971 - 1980, 1998; 32 pages (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - List of fellows., 1983 - 1986; 9 pages (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - University of Minnesota "Johnny Appleseed" program., May 24, 1984 - February 15, 1989; 64 pages; 1 booklet (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Virginia Ball., ca. 1979 - 1988; 37 pages (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Letters from and regarding Barry Farber (radio host)., May 24 - June 15, 1985; 21 pages (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence., April 18, 1978 - December 20, 1985; 60 pages (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Letters of support for N.E.A. grants., 1979 - 1987; 26 pages (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - N.E.A. grant summary., December 6, 1980 - December 10, 1983; 39 pages (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Corporate records., July 1, 1983 - September 30, 1985; 98 pages; 1 poster (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Corporate records., August 25, 1983 - January 6, 1986; 26 pages; 1 poster (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Corporate records., December 10, 1979 - May 11, 1983; 1 volume (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Corporate records., May 12, 1980 - May 11, 1983; 1 volume (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Corporate records., June 19, 1979 - November 14, 1988; 91 pages (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Corporate records., January 2, 1987 - January 26, 1989; 86 pages (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Corporate records., May 14, 1987 - January 26, 1989; 143 pages (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Corporate records., August 13, 1988 - January 3, 1989; 37 pages (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Application inquiries and submissions., 1988; 83 pages (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Application inquiries and submissions., 1988; 76 pages (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Application inquiries and submissions., 1989; 243 pages (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Application inquiries and submissions., 1990; 183 pages (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Application inquiries and submissions., 1991; 94 pages (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Dixie Rinehart (award revoked)., ca. 1983; 72 pages (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Dan Feldman., ca. 1985; 19 pages; negatives (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Robert Steward., ca. 1989 - 1993; 40 pages (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Negatives of I.D. funded designs., ca. 1984 - 1987; 9 sheets of negatives (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Todd Siler., ca. 1982-1983; 45 pages; photographs (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Kent Bailey., ca. 1983 - 1985; 77 pages; 6 slides; photographs (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Belmont Freeman., ca. 1984-1986; 60 pages; 3 negatives; 1 brochure; 1 set blueprints (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Belmont Freeman., ca. 1984 - 1986; 23 pages; 1 book of slides; 1 contact sheet; 3 negatives (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Joel Sokolov., ca. 1984 - 1985; 72 pages; 2 groups of negatives (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Martin Shalsky., ca. 1985 - 1987; 122 pages; 2 groups of negatives (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardees Jody and Keith Baxter., ca. 1985 - 1988; 77 pages; 25 slides; 1 booklet (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding I.D. Fund awardee Glenn Simmons., ca. 1987 - 1989; 53 pages; 1 set of blueprints (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - VHS recording: "The Winning Inventions"; University of Minnesota., 1987; 1 video tape (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Cassette recording: "Special Exposition: Luncheon / John G. Simon.", January 19, 1982; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 24)
    - Cassette recording: "How to Hire a Fundraising Consultant: Ronald LaRose.', January 19, 1982; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 25)
    - Cassette recording: "Innovative Design Fund Meeting"; reader copy on CD., May 9, 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1961 - 1962; 2 volumes
    This subseries contains 2 volumes of financial accounts for Bonnie Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co.
    - Accounting for Cashin's design contracts., 1961; 1 volume (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Accounting for Cashin's design contracts., 1962; 1 volume (Box 218, Folder 2)